<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Logical Defence</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="catlbl">Categories</string>
    <string name="subTitle">The beautiful list of logical fallacies</string>

    <string-array name="sections">
        <item>Appeal to the Mind</item>
        <item>Appeal to the Emotions</item>
        <item>Faulty Deduction</item>
        <item>Garbled Cause &amp; Effect</item>
        <item>Manipulating Content</item>
        <item>On the Attack</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fallacies_titles_1">
        <item>Appeal to Anonymous Authority</item>
        <item>Appeal to Authority</item>
        <item>Appeal to Common Practice</item>
        <item>Appeal to Ignorance</item>
        <item>Appeal to Incredulity</item>
        <item>Appeal to Money</item>
        <item>Appeal to Novelty</item>
        <item>Appeal to Popular Belief</item>
        <item>Appeal to Probability</item>
        <item>Appeal to Tradition</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fallacies_descs_1">
        <item>Using evidence from an unnamed \'expert\' or \'study\' or generalized group (like \'scientists\') to claim something is true.</item>
        <item>Claiming something is true because an (unqualified or untrustworthy) \'expert\' says it is.</item>
        <item>Claiming something is true because it\'s commonly practiced.</item>
        <item>A claim is true simply because it has not been proven false (or false because it has not been proven true).</item>
        <item>Because a claim sounds unbelievable, it must not be true.</item>
        <item>Supposing that, if someone is rich or something is expensive, then it affects the truth of the claim.</item>
        <item>Supposing something is better because it is new or newer.</item>
        <item>Claiming something is true because the majority of people believe it.</item>
        <item>Assuming because something could happen, it will inevitably happen.</item>
        <item>Claiming something is true because it\'s (apparently) always been that way.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fallacies_examples_1">
        <item>\'They say that it takes 7 years to digest chewing gum.\'</item>
        <item>\'Over 4000 prominent scientists and engineers dispute global warming.\'</item>
        <item>\'This bank has some problems with corruption, but there\'s nothing going on here that doesn\'t go on in all other banks.\'</item>
        <item>\'Nobody has proven to me there is a God. So I know there is no God.\'</item>
        <item>\'The eye is an incredibly complex biomechanical machine with thousands of interlocking parts. How could that exist without an intelligent designer?\'</item>
        <item>\'If it costs more, it must be better.\'</item>
        <item>\'Awesome! The latest version of this operating system is going to make my computer faster and better..\'</item>
        <item>\'Milk is essential for healthier bones.\'</item>
        <item>\'There are billions of galaxies with billions of starts in the universe, so there must be another planet with intelligent life on it.\'</item>
        <item>\'The government has always existed, therefore society cannot live without one.\'</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fallacies_titles_2">
        <item>Appeal to Consequences of a Belief</item>
        <item>Appeal to Fear</item>
        <item>Appeal to Flattery</item>
        <item>Appeal to Nature</item>
        <item>Appeal to Pity</item>
        <item>Appeal to Ridicule</item>
        <item>Appeal to Spite</item>
        <item>Appeal to Wishful Thinking</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fallacies_descs_2">
        <item>Arguing a belief is false because it implies something you\'d rather not believe.</item>
        <item>An argument is made by increasing fear and prejudice towards the opposing side.</item>
        <item>Using an irrelevant compliment to slip in an unfounded claim which is accepted along with the compliment.</item>
        <item>Making your claim seem more true by drawing a comparison with the \'good\' natural world.</item>
        <item>Attempt to induce pity to sway opponents.</item>
        <item>Presenting the opponent\'s argument in a way that makes it appear absurd.</item>
        <item>Dismissing a claim by appealing to personal bias against the claimant.</item>
        <item>Suggesting a claim is true or false just because you strongly hope it is.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fallacies_examples_2">
        <item>\'That can\'t be the Senator on that sex-tape. If it were, he\'d be lying about not knowing her, and he\'s not the kind of man who would lie.\'</item>
        <item>\'Before you know there will be more mosques that churches.\'</item>
        <item>\'Intelligent and sophisticated readers will of course recognise a fallacy like this when they read one.\'</item>
        <item>\'Of course homosexuality is unnatural. You don\'t see same-sex animals copulating.\'</item>
        <item>\'The former dictator is an old, dying man. It\'s wrong to make him stand trial for these alleged offenses.\'</item>
        <item>\'Faith in God is like believing in Santa Claus and the Tooth Fairy.\'</item>
        <item>\'Don\'t you just hate how those rich Liberal Hollywood actors go on TV to promote their agendas?\'</item>
        <item>\'The President wouldn\'t lie. He\'s our leader and a good American.\'</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
